geekalerts.com 2014-06-20

# Privacy Policy | GeekAlerts

Your privacy is important to us here at GeekAlerts. Any information you provide will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

## Collection and Use of Information

We collect personally identifiable information such as names and email addresses **only when voluntarily submitted**. This information is used merely to fulfill a specific request, for example, to post a comment on our blog. All emails from us allow you to opt out of further communications.

## Distribution of Information

We never use or share any of those information in ways unrelated to the ones described above. We do not send spam and we do not sell your information to any company for marketing purposes.

## Cookies and Web Beacons

Our site may place a small file, called a cookie, on your hard drive to provide you with a better website. A cookie does not, in any way, give us access to your computer or to any personally identifiable information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. In your browser settings, you can choose to delete and/or not to accept cookies.

Here is a video in which Google explains what cookies do and how they can help web sites and advertisers personalize your online experience:

## Third-party Ads

We allow [third-party vendors](https://www.google.com/adsense/support/bin/answer.py?answer=94149) to serve ads when you visit GeekAlerts. These companies may use information (see “Cookies and Web Beacons”) about your visits in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Read more [about this practice](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies.

## Links to Other Websites

Our site may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you use these links to leave our site, we do not anymore have control over that website. Such sites are not governed by this privacy statement.

_Should you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy, please feel free to[contact us](http://www.geekalerts.com/contact/)._
